["Home Sick" by Benzamin playing]
CLEANING DUTY
AHN SU-HO, YEON SI-EUN, OH BEOM-SEOK
[Su-ho] Ah! Our science teacher's
out of their mind.
Did they put sleeping pills
in their voice?
I was so dazed, I almost passed out.
[Beom-seok chuckles]
It was so boring, I thought even Si-eun
could make the lesson
more interesting if he was teaching.
Nuh-uh. Si-eun's not a talker.
- [chuckles]
- [Su-ho laughs] I don't think so.
Is there any subject
you don't sleep through?
I mean, is there one you actually like?
[Su-ho] What do you know?
You're always looking straight ahead,
pen in hand.
- Forget it.
- [Su-ho] Hmm.
I'm hungry. Let's get somethin' to eat.
I have to get to my job.
Yeong-i took the day off.
See you tomorrow.
[Beom-seok] Si-eun, I, um…
I have something going on at home today.
We can all eat together tomorrow.
I have to go.
[chair scrapes]
[footsteps receding]
[music fades]
[poignant music playing]
[Aide Park] Do you understand
the situation?
Yes. Please come as soon as possible.
[phone bleeps]
[sighs]
Detectives are on their way.
Do you remember what I told you earlier?
[Jeong-chan] Yes, sir.
[Woo-yeong coughs]
Yes.
Tell me what I said.
Uh, well…
We were working out.
He decided to take a break,
then suddenly collapsed.
[Aide Park] And?
[sirens approaching]
[Tae-hun] To make sure
everyone keeps their mouths shut.
If anything goes wrong,
we'll all get sent to juvie.
[Aide Park] You deleted all videos?
[Woo-yeong] Yes.
[Aide Park] I'll check the CCTV footage.
[sirens getting louder]
[ringing tone]
[ringing tone continues]
[sounds echoing]
[no audible dialogue]
[poignant music continues]
WHERE ARE YOU?
I'M WORKING OUT. I'LL CALL YOU LATER
[ringing tone continues]
[music fades]
[door slam echoes]
["Hero" by Meego playing]
WEAK HERO:
CLASS 1
[Jin-won] You little shit.
You're a fucking disgrace.
And you call yourself human? Huh?
[sighs]
[melancholy music playing]
I'll hire a hit man to kill you
as soon as you get to the Philippines.
You're disgusting.
[breathing heavily]
What about Su-ho?
Can you actually believe
this little bastard?
Hey, stay by his side 24-7
until he gets on his flight. Okay?
- Yes, sir.
- You shit.
Stupid son of a bitch.
Fuck!
[footsteps receding]
- [door slams]
- [shudders]
[sobs]
[music fades]
CLASS OF 2022, BYUKSAN HIGH SCHOOL
UNIVERSITY ADMISSIONS
SEOUL NATIONAL UNIVERSITY: 3
YONSEI UNIVERSITY: 7
SOGANG UNIVERSITY: 5
SUNGKYUNKWAN UNIVERSITY: 12
[Yeong-i] We called the police.
I'll keep looking for him too.
You should go home for now.
Your finals are tomorrow.
I'M WORKING OUT. I'LL CALL YOU LATER
[teacher] Don't even think about cheating.
Do your best according
to what you've prepared. All right?
[all] Yes, sir.
[boy 1] How would you feel if I said
I aced the test after you bombed it?
- [boy 2] I slept through it.
- [boy 1] I'm pretty sure I did.
- [boy 2] I'll do an online university.
- [boy 3] Hey, get your phones!
- [boy 2] Never a dull moment.
- [boy 4] Phones!
[boy 1] Actually, I studied pretty hard.
So I'm pretty sure I did all right.
Might have missed a couple.
YEONG-I
MISSED CALL
[bleeps]
[ringing tone]
[sighs]
- [Yeong-i, tearfully] Si-eun-a.
- Yeong-a.
Did you call?
[gasps] Si-eun, it's Su-ho.
[sobbing]
What'll happen to Su-ho?
- ["Self" by Meego playing]
- ♪ Swear to God… ♪
[Yeong-i] It was all because of
that asshole Oh Beom-seok and his gang.
[sobbing]
Some people dropped by
and offered to pay for his hospital bills.
They got his grandmother
to sign something.
[weeping]
[song continues in Korean]
Si-eun-a.
Su-ho won't…
[sobbing]
Su-ho won't wake up.
[continues crying]
- [monitors bleeping]
- [ventilator hissing]
[woman] Are you Su-ho's friend?
Yes.
[woman sighs]
You must be Si-eun, right?
[breathing shakily]
[exhales]
[crying]
[sobbing]
[music fades]
Go to school.
It's your finals week.
I'll stay here, so you should go.
Get some rest.
[sighs]
[door closes]
[suspenseful music playing]
[music fades]
[Aide Park] Go wash up.
The assemblyman
will stop by your school with you.
You're to say goodbye to your teachers.
[groans]
Okay, but…
what about Su-ho?
[poignant music playing]
Su-ho's still alive.
[breathing shakily]
If you want to keep him alive
at the hospital,
you better do as the assemblyman says.
[sighs]
[man on radio] According to the survey,
48.7% of respondents
complained of lack of sleep.
The primary causes of sleep deficiency
included extensive hours
of studying at cram schools,
private tutorials,
homework assignments, and online lectures.
JISEONG HIGH SCHOOL
[mysterious music playing]
[siren blaring in distance]
- Yeah, I know, but--
- [boy 2] Yeah, right?
Which class is Jeon Yeong-bin in?
[music fades]
[Yeong-bin] What's up?
What?
[suspenseful music playing]
[gasping and screaming]
[Yeong-bin yelps]
[groans]
[students scream]
[Yeong-bin wheezing]
[gasps]
Where's that bastard?
- Who?
- [sighs]
- [all gasp]
- [screams]
[groaning]
[whimpers]
[pen clatters]
The damn athlete.
- Your friend.
- [Yeong-bin] In the gym.
He's probably there.
- It was him, right?
- [Yeong-bin shudders]
What was?
Tell me the truth.
I wasn't there yesterday, I promise.
I only saw a video the guys sent.
What video?
I said, "What video?"
[Yeong-bin breathing unsteadily]
This has nothing to do with me.
Oh Beom-seok.
Oh Beom-seok did
all this shit by himself. Look.
[inhales]
[grunts]
It doesn't matter.
[Beom-seok on video] Hey.
[breathing shakily] Stop saying
my fucking name, you cocky shit.
[blows landing]
[Beom-seok] Bitch. You son of a bitch.
- [grunts] Damn it.
- [blows continue]
- [tires screech]
- [Jin-won] Damn it!
Who's that?
Did you put Su-ho into a coma?
[gasps]
It was you, you fucking dick!
Get out of the car!
Get out, you fucking asshole!
Who the fuck do you think you are,
ruining their lives? Huh?
What did Su-ho ever do to you,
you piece of shit?
Come on out, coward!
Don't you even feel bad?
You're a little shithead loser, aren't ya?
[Yeong-i] You fucking bastard!
Get out of the car,
you fucking trash! Come out!
Come face me, you asshole!
[shudders]
[Yeong-i] You fucking coward!
[gasping]
Our group turned to shit after you joined.
It's all your fault.
[sighs]
We got along freaking great
before you showed up.
- [car door opens]
- [Jin-won] Hey!
Get in the car!
- [Aide Park] Let's go.
- [scoffs]
- Don't tell me what to do.
- Handle this.
[car door opens]
- [sighs]
- [car door closes]
[tense music playing]
[sighs]
[punches landing]
JISEONG HIGH SCHOOL
WEIGHT ROOM
[punching continues]
[Si-eun grunts]
[stick clatters]
- [panting]
- [Woo-yeong] Hey.
I can see right through you.
Use your arms
to protect your chin at all times.
Don't forget.
Chin.
[scoffs] What do you want?
You wanna spar with me?
[Su-ho] Next, imagine
there's a punk in front of you.
When this happens,
you don't want to look into his eyes.
Look at his shoulders instead.
Then, when his shoulder comes
toward your face…
[fast, dramatic music playing]
[Woo-yeong] What the fuck?
Come on.
I just told you.
I can see right through you. Get it?
You think… you stand a chance…
against me… you fucking asshole?
- [grunts]
- [gasps]
- [music fades]
- [high-pitched ringing]
[Su-ho] The next step is
to take your fists and beat…
Run.
It's better just to run…
because you might get hurt fighting him.
[gasps] I don't wanna run.
[chuckles] What?
[Si-eun grunting]
[dramatic music resumes]
[Woo-yeong grunting]
[shoelace creaking]
[yells]
Asshole!
[groans]
[screams]
[music fades]
[groans]
Wait. Wait.
Ahn Su-ho
was hurt that bad 'cause Oh Beom-seok
kicked his head so many times.
I have nothing to do with this. Fuck!
- [whimpering]
- Oh yeah?
- Okay.
- Listen to me, dude!
I only sparred Ahn Su-ho in a match!
Hey, please stop this. Yeah? All right?
I apologize, okay? Huh?
[gasping]
Don't apologize to me.
[crunching]
[screams]
[groans]
[moans]
- [groans]
- [Si-eun sighs]
SCHOOL WHERE THE STUDENTS
AND THE TEACHERS ARE HAPPY
[insects chirping]
- Hello!
- Were you all waiting for me?
Assemblyman, it's a pleasure.
We appreciate you making the time
to pay us a visit.
Oh, not at all.
This was long overdue. [chuckles]
Life gets in the way.
- [teacher] This is our faculty.
- [Ji-won] Yes.
[Ji-won] I heard,
about two days ago,
a student here was seriously injured.
Well, yes.
He was working out at the gym
with his friends the other night,
when he collapsed, suddenly,
while taking a little break.
It was an accident.
Oh, that's awful.
[teacher] Yes.
[Ji-won sighs]
[papers rustling]
[teacher pacing slowly]
[birdsong]
[dramatic, suspenseful music playing]
[Si-eun sighs]
Did something happen?
Is that blood?
[students murmuring]
[teacher] Si-eun-a.
Why is there blood on your uniform?
What the fuck, man?
- [boy 1] Oh!
- [Tae-hun] Shit!
Oh fuck!
Fuck, man. Hey.
Please. Hey, calm down, okay?
- Oh fuck.
- [Tae-hun] Let's talk it out! Fuck!
Let's just talk it out! Come on!
[fire extinguisher clangs]
[Tae-hun] Oh my God, he's fucking crazy.
- [boy 1] Oh shit.
- [Jeong-chan] Oh, no.
Don't come near me.
Stay away!
Go away!
Fuck you, man!
[students gasp]
[Tae-hun] Fuck you, shithead.
[Tae-hun coughing]
[groans]
[students gasp]
[breathing unsteadily]
[students murmuring]
[music fades]
[sighs]
I asked you…
to stop.
Just do it.
We were all close.
Hit me already.
[students gasp]
[all murmuring]
Fuck you.
Why?
Why'd you do it?
[breathing shakily]
I have no idea why I did it.
["Again" by Han playing]
♪ I miss the memories, I miss your tune… ♪
You should understand me, Si-eun-a.
♪ I miss the compliments
The smile on your face… ♪
Yeah.
I do.
♪ It was only just yesterday… ♪
So I need…
you to understand me, too.
♪ It's summer already
Still I don't know what to do ♪
[sobbing]
[clattering]
[murmuring]
♪ How deep are you?
No tracks to follow you… ♪
- What is everyone doing out in the hall?
- ♪ How real am I to face you hollow? ♪
[teacher 1] Who is that?
- Where's he going? Stop him.
- [teacher 2] It looks like Si-eun.
- Yeon Si-eun.
- [teacher 3] Hey, Si-eun!
- [teacher 4] Go back inside.
- [teacher 2] Si-eun-a!
[teacher 3] Hey.
- [teacher 2] Yeon Si-eun.
- [teacher 3] Yeon Si-eun.
Yeon Si-eun!
- Hey!
- [students gasping]
What do you fucking want?
♪ I feel my faith, my heart is racin' ♪
♪ I wanna dive into your warmth ♪
♪ Even if I do ♪
♪ Even if I trust you ♪
♪ Do you feel nothin'? ♪
♪I finally do make up my mind… ♪
- [monitors bleeping]
- [ventilator hissing]
♪ It's time I lose you for good ♪
[music fades]
[Si-eun sighs]
[sighs]
[sounds fade]
[Su-ho] Si-eun-a, how can you sleep?
[chuckles]
'Cause…
I'm tired.
[chuckles]
You really are
a psycho, you know that?
Yeah?
I'm sorry.
For what?
Everything.
Me too.
Sorry.
["Home Sick" by Benzamin playing]
- [monitors bleeping]
- [ventilator hissing]
[sniffles]
[sobbing]
[sobbing continues]
["Home Sick" continues]
[Si-eun] Beom-seok…
left to study abroad.
[woman] It was in Paris! Come on.
[indistinct chatter]
["Home Sick" continues]
[Si-eun] Yeong-i said
everything was her fault.
She apologized and then disappeared.
I hear she gives Su-ho's grandmother
a call from time to time,
but I can never reach her.
Beom-seok's father tried
to send me to a juvie center.
But I was only forced to transfer schools
because I agreed to keep quiet
about what happened to Su-ho.
However, he had already made sure
all the schools in Seoul rejected me.
Only Eunjang High School in Yeongdeungpo
was willing to accept me.
EUNJANG HIGH SCHOOL
[music fades]
Si-eun-a.
I'll go with you.
I should introduce myself
to your homeroom teacher.
It's okay. I'll go alone.
[father] You did well.
You did absolutely nothing wrong.
- Hey, stupid!
- Come on! He's wussin' out!
- Hey, hey! Hey!
- Punk ass!
You gotta punch! You gotta punch!
- Like that, all right?
- Aim for the midsection!
All right. Go on!
Man.
[boy 1] Come on!
- Okay, come on.
- [boy 2 groans]
- Nice one!
- You got that?
Everyone, back in your seats. Come on.
- [boy 3] Like that, man!
- [teacher] Sit down!
[students murmuring]
Hey! I have arrived.
[silence]
[clears throat]
We have a transfer student.
Introduce yourself.
I'm Yeon Si-eun.
Nice to meet you.
- [giggling]
- [boy 4] Look at his face.
[teacher] Si-eun-a,
you can sit over there.
[indistinct chatter]
[boy 5] Hi.
[boy 1] How many?
I'm not… Wow! Okay. All right. I think I…
[clang]
Yeon Si-eun. That's pretty.
What are you, a girl?
[laughs]
Hey, bro, what's up with your eyes?
Your stare makes me feel like shit.
What a fucking asshole.
It's getting a little chilly in here.
- [laughter]
- [boy 2] Huh?
[boy 1] Ooh!
[boy 5 sighs]
[unsettling music playing]
You're mine now, bitch.
You all…
are disappointingly predictable.
What?
Do you think…
this makes you look cool?
What the hell's
this son of a bitch saying? [scoffs]
Shut it, or I'll smash your fucking teeth.
[creaking]
[music intensifying]
[music fades]
["Brass Knuckle" by Boi B playing]
[music stops]
[man] This prick just transferred
to Eunjang High.
He beat up Kang Woo-yeong,
the alliance candidate.
What should I do?
["Home Sick" by Benzamin playing]
♪ Baby, I don't know how to go home
Now I'm sick… ♪
[lyrics in Korean]
♪ Baby, I don't know how to go home
Now I'm sick… ♪
[lyrics in Korean]
♪ Pouring… ♪
♪ Puffing, I'll figure it out… ♪
[lyrics in Korean]
♪ I know that…
♪ Baby, I don't know how to go home
Now I'm sick… ♪
[lyrics in Korean]
♪ Baby, I don't know how to go home
Now I'm sick… ♪
[lyrics in Korean]
♪ I don't know how to go home again… ♪
♪ The window shows another conscience
You can't find me…♪
[lyrics in Korean]
♪ I sing along with my rival… ♪
♪ Baby, I don't know how to go home
Now I'm sick… ♪
[lyrics in Korean]
♪ Baby, I don't know how to go home
Now I'm sick… ♪
[lyrics in Korean]
♪ No one's beside me… ♪
♪ Boy, I get so wild
For my love of probs, yeah… ♪
[lyrics in Korean]
♪ The door shine again… ♪
♪ Baby, I don't know how to go home
Now I'm sick… ♪
[lyrics in Korean]
♪ Baby, I don't know how to go home
Now I'm sick… ♪
ALL NAMES, PLACES, AND EVENTS
ARE FICTIONAL
ANY SIMILARITY TO REALITY IS COINCIDENTAL
[lyrics in Korean]
[music fades]